<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-05-07T09:53:39-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">BootlegPotato</title><entry><title type="html">May 6 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/May-6th-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="May 6 Update" /><published>2019-05-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/May-6th-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/May-6th-update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Blog is still up an running&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AnxiousPotato.com Blog
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Version 0.1 is effectively done. In this version there are three blogs: Project, Art, and Hobby. With the project and art blogs the being combined into the front facing blog and the hobby blog being isolated into its own section of the site.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’m currently back posting content to Hobby blog from my Instagram account and then I’ll be reviewing the old Blogger powered blog for any content worth back posting before I go live.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) Blog is still up an running AnxiousPotato.com Blog Version 0.1 is effectively done. In this version there are three blogs: Project, Art, and Hobby. With the project and art blogs the being combined into the front facing blog and the hobby blog being isolated into its own section of the site. I’m currently back posting content to Hobby blog from my Instagram account and then I’ll be reviewing the old Blogger powered blog for any content worth back posting before I go live.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April 23 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/April-23rd-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April 23 Update" /><published>2019-04-23T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/April-23rd-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/April-23rd-update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;jekyll-paginate-v2 doesn’t work in GitHub Pages. I read the warning and wanted to see for my self. The solution is to publish static output pages directly to GitHub. Turns out that was a recommended solution stated somewhere else.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Updated the blog pages to live in a blog directory.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Updated some page styles. Bold is now light green and links are light green with an underline. The page header and footer are now separated from the page content by a dashed line going full width across the page.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Add top nav with a links to GitHub profile and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bootlegpotato.com/&quot;&gt;@BootlegPotato&lt;/a&gt; hub site.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Item&lt;/strong&gt;: Update title in 404 page to link back to index.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I Got The Dumbs&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m not very good at setting the date front matter.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) jekyll-paginate-v2 doesn’t work in GitHub Pages. I read the warning and wanted to see for my self. The solution is to publish static output pages directly to GitHub. Turns out that was a recommended solution stated somewhere else. Updated the blog pages to live in a blog directory. Updated some page styles. Bold is now light green and links are light green with an underline. The page header and footer are now separated from the page content by a dashed line going full width across the page. Add top nav with a links to GitHub profile and @BootlegPotato hub site. New Item: Update title in 404 page to link back to index. I Got The Dumbs: I’m not very good at setting the date front matter.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April 22 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/April-22nd-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April 22 Update" /><published>2019-04-22T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/April-22nd-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/April-22nd-update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Implemented jekyll-paginate-v2 and I have no idea if it works on GitHub Pages. (spoiler it doesn’t)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Will need to figure out how to do multiple category blogs for future projects.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Untitled Mini Game Collection
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gbstudio.dev/&quot;&gt;GB Studio&lt;/a&gt; looks interesting.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) Implemented jekyll-paginate-v2 and I have no idea if it works on GitHub Pages. (spoiler it doesn’t) Will need to figure out how to do multiple category blogs for future projects. Untitled Mini Game Collection GB Studio looks interesting.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Its Alive!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/its-alive.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Its Alive!" /><published>2019-04-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/its-alive</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/its-alive.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;current-projects&quot;&gt;Current projects&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Working on turning this GitHub Pages design into a Jekyll theme.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Still need to work out the pagination.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cleaning up a repo of various mini game projects for public release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Current projects Working on turning this GitHub Pages design into a Jekyll theme. Still need to work out the pagination. Cleaning up a repo of various mini game projects for public release.</summary></entry></feed>