<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-07-21T15:47:13-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">BootlegPotato</title><entry><title type="html">July 21 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/07/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="July 21 Update" /><published>2019-07-21T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-07-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/07/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/07/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bootleg Comix
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Uploaded a bunch of new Post-It Note drawings to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bootlegcomix.com/gallery/mug/&quot;&gt;Mugshots&lt;/a&gt; gallery.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anxious Potato
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Back posted a few posts to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/&quot;&gt;AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Fixed pagination for the primary blog. Just found out that it is broke for any of the filtered blogs.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bootleg Potato
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Trying to focus more on the blog so I updated &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bootlegpotato.com/&quot;&gt;@BootlegPotato&lt;/a&gt; so that the Bootleg Comix and Anxious Potato cards/buttons are swapped.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Bootleg Comix Uploaded a bunch of new Post-It Note drawings to the Mugshots gallery. Anxious Potato Back posted a few posts to AnxiousPotato.com. Fixed pagination for the primary blog. Just found out that it is broke for any of the filtered blogs. Bootleg Potato Trying to focus more on the blog so I updated @BootlegPotato so that the Bootleg Comix and Anxious Potato cards/buttons are swapped.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">July 18 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/07/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="July 18 Update" /><published>2019-07-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-07-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/07/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/07/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bootleg Comix
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Working on adding project section that groups related art together. This might be an entirely manual process unlike the art gallery section where I use Jekyll to build a gallery at least once.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Card Game
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’ve made two version of the card frame/borders. One is for digital illustration and the other is for Post-It note drawings that hopefully leans into the fact that they are drawn on paper. I need to post those to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/&quot;&gt;AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I also made card icons that I should really post on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/&quot;&gt;AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt; as well.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anxious Potato
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I did post two overviews of the art/drawing tools that carry around with me that was originally post on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pillowfort.social/BootlegPotato&quot;&gt;PillowFort.social&lt;/a&gt;. My tools have changed so I should do an update.
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/blog/art/2019/06/pens01.html&quot;&gt;Art Tools Part One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/blog/art/2019/06/pens02.html&quot;&gt;Art Tools Part Two&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;GitHub Blog (This Site)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Just fixed the pagination while writing this post&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Bootleg Comix Working on adding project section that groups related art together. This might be an entirely manual process unlike the art gallery section where I use Jekyll to build a gallery at least once. Card Game I’ve made two version of the card frame/borders. One is for digital illustration and the other is for Post-It note drawings that hopefully leans into the fact that they are drawn on paper. I need to post those to AnxiousPotato.com I also made card icons that I should really post on AnxiousPotato.com as well. Anxious Potato I did post two overviews of the art/drawing tools that carry around with me that was originally post on PillowFort.social. My tools have changed so I should do an update. Art Tools Part One Art Tools Part Two GitHub Blog (This Site) Just fixed the pagination while writing this post</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">June 20 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/06/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="June 20 Update" /><published>2019-06-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-06-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/06/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/06/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cabinet of Blunder
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Moved the hobby blog to its own domain at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cabinetofblunder.com/&quot;&gt;CabinetOfBlunder.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Still backposting old content.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Card Game
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I bounced some ideas off of a buddy and I think we worked out how the “challenge” of the challenge deck could work.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Cabinet of Blunder Moved the hobby blog to its own domain at CabinetOfBlunder.com. Still backposting old content. Card Game I bounced some ideas off of a buddy and I think we worked out how the “challenge” of the challenge deck could work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">June 10 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/06/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="June 10 Update" /><published>2019-06-10T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-06-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/06/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/06/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bootleg Comix
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The updated &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bootlegcomix.com/&quot;&gt;BootlegComix.com&lt;/a&gt; is live. I’m kind of surprised that I got far enough alone to go live with it.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Still need to rebuild the randomized site icon feature. Probably should remake and update the icon as well.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Gallery titles need to be updated to H2 and resized at the md breakpoint (probably).&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Need to make better gallery icons/cover images.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Need to update Inktober and March of Robots galleries with character information (again).&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;All sites (including AnxiousPotato.com) need pagination updated.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Need to update the About page because it still references the Minima Jekyll theme.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Card Game
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The five way &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rock%E2%80%93paper%E2%80%93scissors&quot;&gt;Roshambo&lt;/a&gt; is clunkier than intended. I’m going to see if a traditional three way improves game flow. I’ll also consider just using a simple point system which would make card colors thematic rather than a mechanic.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Bootleg Comix The updated BootlegComix.com is live. I’m kind of surprised that I got far enough alone to go live with it. Still need to rebuild the randomized site icon feature. Probably should remake and update the icon as well. Gallery titles need to be updated to H2 and resized at the md breakpoint (probably). Need to make better gallery icons/cover images. Need to update Inktober and March of Robots galleries with character information (again). All sites (including AnxiousPotato.com) need pagination updated. BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) Need to update the About page because it still references the Minima Jekyll theme. Card Game The five way Roshambo is clunkier than intended. I’m going to see if a traditional three way improves game flow. I’ll also consider just using a simple point system which would make card colors thematic rather than a mechanic.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">May 31 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="May 31 Update" /><published>2019-05-31T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-31T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anxious Potato
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/&quot;&gt;AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt; has been updated to be a project blog or rather just my blog.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bootleg Comix
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Currently in the process of updating &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bootlegcomix.com/&quot;&gt;BootlegComix.com&lt;/a&gt; with Jekyll.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The recent comic strip and archive is built using Jekyll’s blog functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’m going to see if I can build the ongoing image galleries using the blog functionality as well.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Need to update the pagination buttons.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Card Game
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I posted a picture of some prototype cards over on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/blog/art/2019/05/card-proto.html&quot;&gt;AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt;. I need to decided if I’m going to maintain a GitHub repo for this project and what form that would take. Considering that it would mostly be images, I’ll need to figure out how small I can get the file sizes for images so I don’t run into GitHub’s repo size limit.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Anxious Potato AnxiousPotato.com has been updated to be a project blog or rather just my blog. Bootleg Comix Currently in the process of updating BootlegComix.com with Jekyll. The recent comic strip and archive is built using Jekyll’s blog functionality. I’m going to see if I can build the ongoing image galleries using the blog functionality as well. Need to update the pagination buttons. Card Game I posted a picture of some prototype cards over on AnxiousPotato.com. I need to decided if I’m going to maintain a GitHub repo for this project and what form that would take. Considering that it would mostly be images, I’ll need to figure out how small I can get the file sizes for images so I don’t run into GitHub’s repo size limit.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">May 27 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="May 27 Update" /><published>2019-05-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hobby Blog
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hobby.anxiouspotato.com&quot;&gt;hobby.AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt; is up and running.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Still need to implement pagination, random site banner, rss, and a few other features but progress not perfection.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cleaned up the Gemfile by removing the github plugin. I’m maintaining the Jekyll project in a separate repo and publishing the _site file to the github pages repo (this repo).&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cleaned up post file names. The new format isn’t great for SEO but SEO shouldn’t take priority over a project primary purpose.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ace Delivery Collection
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I republished the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/BootlegPotato/Ace-Delivery-Collection&quot;&gt;mini game repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Hobby Blog hobby.AnxiousPotato.com is up and running. Still need to implement pagination, random site banner, rss, and a few other features but progress not perfection. BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) Cleaned up the Gemfile by removing the github plugin. I’m maintaining the Jekyll project in a separate repo and publishing the _site file to the github pages repo (this repo). Cleaned up post file names. The new format isn’t great for SEO but SEO shouldn’t take priority over a project primary purpose. Ace Delivery Collection I republished the mini game repo.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">May 23 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="May 23 Update" /><published>2019-05-23T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hobby Blog
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The Hobby Blog getting spun out into its own site. The current plan is to host it as a subdomain of AnxiousPotato.com. In my head this freed me from trying to back post old content before going live. I’m currently working on the logo and styles.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AnxiousPotato.com
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.anxiouspotato.com/&quot;&gt;AnxiousPotato.com&lt;/a&gt; has been done but I don’t want to cut over until I migrate the art galleries to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bootlegcomix.com/&quot;&gt;BootlegComix.com&lt;/a&gt;. The thing is that those galleries are hosted on DeviantArt or PillowFort. I just need to get over it.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Card Game
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I started working on a simple card game that is effectively just vehicle for me to draw card sized illustrations. The central mechanic is a five way roshambo.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ace Delivery Collection
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I need to make a note and publish the mini game collection to GitHub.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update Hobby Blog The Hobby Blog getting spun out into its own site. The current plan is to host it as a subdomain of AnxiousPotato.com. In my head this freed me from trying to back post old content before going live. I’m currently working on the logo and styles. AnxiousPotato.com AnxiousPotato.com has been done but I don’t want to cut over until I migrate the art galleries to BootlegComix.com. The thing is that those galleries are hosted on DeviantArt or PillowFort. I just need to get over it. Card Game I started working on a simple card game that is effectively just vehicle for me to draw card sized illustrations. The central mechanic is a five way roshambo. Ace Delivery Collection I need to make a note and publish the mini game collection to GitHub.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">May 6 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="May 6 Update" /><published>2019-05-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/05/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Blog is still up an running&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AnxiousPotato.com Blog
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Version 0.1 is effectively done. In this version there are three blogs: Project, Art, and Hobby. With the project and art blogs the being combined into the front facing blog and the hobby blog being isolated into its own section of the site.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I’m currently back posting content to Hobby blog from my Instagram account and then I’ll be reviewing the old Blogger powered blog for any content worth back posting before I go live.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) Blog is still up an running AnxiousPotato.com Blog Version 0.1 is effectively done. In this version there are three blogs: Project, Art, and Hobby. With the project and art blogs the being combined into the front facing blog and the hobby blog being isolated into its own section of the site. I’m currently back posting content to Hobby blog from my Instagram account and then I’ll be reviewing the old Blogger powered blog for any content worth back posting before I go live.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April 23 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April 23 Update" /><published>2019-04-23T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;jekyll-paginate-v2 doesn’t work in GitHub Pages. I read the warning and wanted to see for my self. The solution is to publish static output pages directly to GitHub. Turns out that was a recommended solution stated somewhere else.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Updated the blog pages to live in a blog directory.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Updated some page styles. Bold is now light green and links are light green with an underline. The page header and footer are now separated from the page content by a dashed line going full width across the page.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Add top nav with a links to GitHub profile and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bootlegpotato.com/&quot;&gt;@BootlegPotato&lt;/a&gt; hub site.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Item&lt;/strong&gt;: Update title in 404 page to link back to index.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I Got The Dumbs&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m not very good at setting the date front matter.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) jekyll-paginate-v2 doesn’t work in GitHub Pages. I read the warning and wanted to see for my self. The solution is to publish static output pages directly to GitHub. Turns out that was a recommended solution stated somewhere else. Updated the blog pages to live in a blog directory. Updated some page styles. Bold is now light green and links are light green with an underline. The page header and footer are now separated from the page content by a dashed line going full width across the page. Add top nav with a links to GitHub profile and @BootlegPotato hub site. New Item: Update title in 404 page to link back to index. I Got The Dumbs: I’m not very good at setting the date front matter.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April 22 Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April 22 Update" /><published>2019-04-22T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2019/04/update.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;project-update&quot;&gt;Project Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Implemented jekyll-paginate-v2 and I have no idea if it works on GitHub Pages. (spoiler it doesn’t)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Will need to figure out how to do multiple category blogs for future projects.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Untitled Mini Game Collection
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gbstudio.dev/&quot;&gt;GB Studio&lt;/a&gt; looks interesting.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>BootlegPotato</name></author><summary type="html">Project Update BootlegPotato.GitHub.io Page (This page) Implemented jekyll-paginate-v2 and I have no idea if it works on GitHub Pages. (spoiler it doesn’t) Will need to figure out how to do multiple category blogs for future projects. Untitled Mini Game Collection GB Studio looks interesting.</summary></entry></feed>